(Penny:)Pants, but Leonard says
sex doesn't count.
Hm. You poor thing.
(Raj:)You have one arrow in your quiver,
and you just can't use it.
(Raj:)Fortunately, another pathway
to a man's heart
(Raj:)is through his stomach.
I don't know if I want to cock
for him; he's kind of a picky eater.
I mean, "It's too salty.
It's too dry.
(Penny:)It's too burnt and frozen
at the same time."
Wait, come on, what else
would sweep you off your feet?
(Raj:)Well, I've always had this fantasy
that involves dancing.
(Raj:)The sexual chemistry between
my partner and me is electric.
(Raj:)But boy, oh, boy,
does my father not approve
(Raj:)until he sees us
in the big dance competition.
(Penny:)Okay, that's just the plot
for Dirty Dancing.
(Penny:)What else would you love,
other than
(Penny:)being lifted
over Patrick Swayze's head?
Oh, oh. You could
stand outside his window
(Raj:)with a boom box in the air.
(Penny:)That's from Say Anything.